When you talk about it being overwhelming, tell me more about that feeling.
Is it just like shocking, like surprising?
Is it fulfilling?
Is it healing?
It's not surprising because I knew my intent in creating.
And my intention in creating was being able to create a space where we can be unapologetic.
Why is that important in this iteration of Black pop culture?
Where else we gonna do it?
It's one thing to say I'm doing it in my life, but I'm constantly gonna hit opposition.
I'm gonna constantly hit these obstacles.
I'm constantly gonna hit people telling me, no, you can't do that.
Or you can't say that.
Or where are you going?
You can get that on the edit, in the script, you know what I'm saying?
But once you have identified what this is, the script is there, you fall in the pocket.